<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<topic xmlns="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1  http://www.imsglobal.org/profile/cc/ccv1p1/ccv1p1_imsdt_v1p1.xsd">
  <title>The UF Department of Geography is recruiting motivated students to participate in the summer 2025 GeoGator Summer Undergraduate Research Experience!</title>
  <text texttype="text/html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span data-olk-copy-source="MessageBody"&gt;Applications will close at the end of this week (2/23)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The UF GeoGator Summer Undergraduate Research Experience is a research opportunity for undergraduate students to participate in an active research project with a faculty member in the Geography department. The program provides students with the opportunity to gain hands-on experience, the chance to be involved with cutting edge research and lab environments, the opportunity to identify and develop career-related skills and abilities, and also provide a chance to network with professionals.&amp;nbsp;This program aims to prepare students for future careers by gaining valuable and marketable experience, and expanding their knowledge beyond the classroom. This for-credit research experience will launch during 2025’s Summer C term.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Visit the&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a name="x__Hlk190695412"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a title="https://geog.ufl.edu/geogator-summer-research-program/" href="https://geog.ufl.edu/geogator-summer-research-program/" target="_blank" data-auth="NotApplicable" data-linkindex="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;i&gt;GeoGator Summer Undergraduate Research Experience&amp;nbsp; website&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;to explore potential summer research projects, find more information about the summer schedule, and to apply!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Questions about the GeoGator Summer Undergraduate Research Experience should be directed to the program coordinator, Dr. Gabriela Hamerlinck (&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a title="mailto:ghamerlinck@ufl.edu" href="mailto:ghamerlinck@ufl.edu" data-linkindex="1"&gt;&lt;i&gt;ghamerlinck@ufl.edu&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;).&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
</topic>
