<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<topic xmlns="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1  http://www.imsglobal.org/profile/cc/ccv1p1/ccv1p1_imsdt_v1p1.xsd">
  <title>Boost Your Remote Sensing Expertise – Register for Advanced Remote Sensing (GEO4938/GEO6038)!</title>
  <text texttype="text/html">&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to let you know about an excellent opportunity to further develop your remote sensing skills this Fall semester: Advanced Remote Sensing (GEO4938/GEO6038).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This course takes your remote sensing knowledge to the next level by focusing on cutting-edge Earth observation technologies, including:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LiDAR: Analyze 3D point clouds, terrain modeling, and forest structure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hyperspectral Imaging: Advanced techniques in spectral unmixing and ecosystem analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time Series Analysis: Multi-temporal change detection, phenological cycle modeling, and environmental monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The course is taught by Dr. Di Yang and is designed to provide extensive hands-on experience with airborne and terrestrial data, sophisticated analytical techniques, and practical projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, this class counts as an elective towards your Geospatial Information Analyst Certificate, making it a smart choice to advance both your skills and credentials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Course Details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Semester: Fall 2025&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location: Turlington Hall 3006&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instructor: Dr. Di Yang&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prerequisites: None&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seats may fill quickly, so I encourage you to register soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to reach out if you have questions or need more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Best,&lt;br&gt;Dr. Sounny&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="$IMS-CC-FILEBASE$/Uploaded%20Media/Screenshot%202025-04-17%20at%209.00.31%E2%80%AFPM.png" alt="Screenshot 2025-04-17 at 9.00.31 PM.png" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
</topic>
